res.net 2019-05-15

# RES.NET - Your Trusted Mortgage Banking Service Provider - Privacy Statement

Welcome and thank you for visiting our Privacy Policy. It is important that you familiarize yourself with the terms of our Privacy Policy so that you will be aware of the kind of information that we gather, how we may use that information as well as how and in what circumstance we may share that information. We commit to give each of our website visitors, users and customers quality service. Because of this commitment, we gather information about our website visitors, users and customers so we can better serve you. We realize and appreciate that privacy is important to you. Please know that your privacy is also important to us. Whether you are a website visitor, user or our customer, you can be comfortable that we respect the confidentiality of the personal identifiable information that identifies you. We will treat the personal identifiable information that you provide to us in a responsible manner. We do not participate in the selling or renting of your personal identifiable information to third parties for their business purposes. 

By visiting this website, using this website or becoming our customer, you accept the terms and practices described in this Privacy Policy, which is effective as of October 8, 2010, and is part of our Terms and Conditions of Use which govern the use of this website unless expressly provided otherwise relating to another specific service offered by us. For instance, if another one of our services expressly provides for different applicable terms and conditions of use, separate or additional privacy policy, or other policy, then those separate terms and conditions of use, privacy policy, or other policy shall apply in connection with your use of that specific service. We may change, modify, alter or add to this Privacy Policy from time to time. When that happens, we will post the revised Privacy Policy here. Any use by you of this website or use of any of our services after changes to this Privacy Policy have been posted will constitute your knowledge and acceptance of those changes (meaning that the changes may be applied to the information we previously collected or may collect thereafter from and about you).

We are not responsible for the terms and conditions of use, practices or policies relating to the privacy policy or data collection of personal identifiable information of the websites from which you access our website, of websites that this website may we link to, or of any websites that are linked to our website.

This Privacy Policy informs you about the kinds of information we collect about our visitors, users and customers; how we use that information; how we may share it with others; and how you can access and change the information we gathered about you. If you have questions about our privacy practices that are not resolved from your review of our Privacy Policy or you would like more information about our Privacy Policy, please contact [privacy@res.net](mailto:privacy@res.net)

####### PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM OUR VISITORS, USERS AND CUSTOMERS

We gather personal information about you so we can deliver better service to you. We make reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal and other information is secure and to treat that personal and other information in a responsible manner. We collect the personal information that you voluntarily give us and that you give us in response to our request when you choose to purchase a product from us or use one of our services. For example, when you register with this website, you will be asked to provide personal and other information such as your name, e-mail address, physical address, and telephone number. Registration is generally required to use the functions of this website. Likewise, we will ask you to provide contact information if you use one of our services that connects you to other visitors, users, customers, affiliated businesses or third party providers of goods, products or services, if you request that we send you e-newsletters or other promotional notices or if you seek information or assistance from us. 

If you purchase a good, product or service, we will ask you for financial information such as your credit card number, debit card number, bank account routing and account number or other financial information in addition to asking for your telephone number, billing address, your preferred shipping address and other information we may believe is pertinent. We may gather additional personal information from you in relation with your use of certain optional services or features offered within or through our website. If you register or elect to receive e-mails, messages or e-newsletters, you may be asked to provide information concerning your personal interests. We may also collect personal information from the criteria of your search lists, characteristics of your wish lists or reminders.

You understand and accept that when and if you upload video/audio/graphic/data content to this website containing your personal information, that you voluntarily place such content in a domain that may be collected and/ or used by other third parties. When you upload such content to this website you do so at your own risk and you agree to assume all responsibility for this action and the corresponding consequences. You further agree to hold this website, its owners, officers, directors, employees, agents and representatives harmless for any and all harm, injury, damage and liability associated with your election to upload such content into this website.

####### OTHER KINDS OF COLLECTED VISITOR, USER OR CUSTOMER INFORMATION

We may also obtain personal information about you such as contact information, updated address, shipping instructions and credit information from agents, consultants, contractors, carriers or other third parties. We may also collect contact and other information about prospective customers so that they may be contacted concerning goods, products or services that we believe may be of interest to them.

Additionally, our computer and software systems keep track of technical information about your computer or mobile device, such as the browser type and version; browser plug-in types and versions, and operating system of your computer; the Internet Service Provider (ISP) or other provider you use to access certain of our services; and your internet protocol (IP) address, location, and time zone setting. These computer and software systems automatically collect information about how you were directed to them; how you navigate around them; what channels, groups, associations, favorites and networks you enroll in; what other users, visitors or customers with whom you elect to communicate; the content you watch; the size and frequency that you may upload or download content to or from this website; the nature, substance and relevance of the content that you may upload or download to or from this website; what goods, products or services you browse; and your purchasing activities to help us to better understand the use of our website and services by our website visitors, users and customers; to improve your experience; and to aid us in marketing and managing our services.

####### HOW THIS INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

When you register with this website, we compile the personal information you give us about yourself into an individual profile and thereafter add other personal information about you to that profile as we obtain it. We also collect information about your actions in using this website; the content that you choose to view, upload and download within, to, or from this website; the purchases you make; and other uses of our website and services as they occur. Personal and other information about prospective customers may be collected by us or obtained from our business partners or other third parties. 

Our computer and software systems automatically gather other information (including the technical information identified above) when you access certain features of our website and services, including through the use of cookies and web beacons.

####### USE OF COOKIES

Cookies enhance our ability to serve you. Cookies are pieces of text that a website stores on your computer – an identification code of sorts. This cookie can be accessed by the website when you revisit it. We use two types of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies terminate shortly after you terminate your internet session. Persistent cookies are stored on your hard drive until they expire or are deleted. Both types of cookies help provide an enhanced user experience since they recall your use of the Internet, this website and our services, shopping preferences, shopping cart information, and your password.

We understand that not everyone wants to permit the use of cookies. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies and how to disable cookies, but we recommend that you leave cookies turned on so that you can take full advantage of the shopping features we offer.

####### USE OF WEB BEACONS

Web beacons are small, transparent graphics that are placed on web pages to track how visitors arrive at a website and what they do there. We use web beacons to track customers' visits to and browsing activities at our website and to compile sales and statistical data. This information assists us in marketing and managing our website and enhancing your experience with us.

####### REQUIREMENT TO PROVIDE REQUESTED PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information is required for you to use this website, become a customer, make a purchase, request information or assistance, or take advantage of certain services and features we offer.

####### HOW WE PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION

Credit information is encrypted by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software when it is transmitted to us via the Internet to any website address beginning with https. The servers that store this information are located in a facility with restricted access. We also truncate your credit card number to the last four digits when we communicate with you about your order.

####### USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT OUR CUSTOMERS

We use your personal information to better target the information you access in and through this website, to fulfill and process your orders and to connect you with other goods, products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. This includes for example, contacting you to confirm your order, fulfilling it, and delivering it. We may also contact you about your order.

Additionally, we will use your contact information to send you e-newsletters or other promotional notices, or to respond to requests for information or assistance from you.

We may also use your personal information to improve our service to you, to customize the content you see, and for research, marketing, and other business purposes. For example, we periodically review customer information as part of servicing our accounts. We may also contact you from time to time to inform you of the services that we offer and to gather information about how we can improve them.

Finally, we analyze information we obtain automatically from our computer and software systems, including from cookies and web beacons, concerning our customers' use of, access to, and navigation of our services and their browsing and purchasing activities to improve, customize, and market our services and content, to enhance our visitor, user and customer experience, and for research, marketing, and other business purposes.

####### WE SOMETIMES SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

Please be reminded that the primary purpose and function of this website is to create a forum for people and businesses interested in the real estate industry; including, but limited to lenders, servicers, asset managers, brokers, agents, appraisers, attorneys, title companies and others engaged in or associated with the real estate industry and to share information about specific real property and about themselves in the form of video, audio, graphics, data, photographs and other forms with the specific intent and understanding that such information will be distributed through this website, associated websites and possibly redistributed through the internet and other mediums or channels. Personal information that will or may be made public that you choose to share with this website may include, but is not limited to, your name, your account name, your gender, your photograph, your address, your e-mail address, your telephone number, your professional license number(s), the date you opened your account, the date you uploaded information or content, the number of pieces of information or content that you have uploaded, the last date that you uploaded information or content, the date that downloaded information or content, the number of pieces of information or content that you have downloaded, the last date that you downloaded information or content, your opinions and comments about information and content that is displayed or accessible through this website and other features about you that you may provide.

In order to receive and process your orders and requests, we may provide your name, address, and other personal information, such as your e-mail address and telephone number, to other entities such as credit card companies (for example, American Express, Visa, UPS, and USPS). Similarly, if you order a product that is shipped directly from another company, or offered by us in conjunction with another company, we will share personal information about that order with the other company.

We may use third party agents, consultants, and contractors to perform business functions on our behalf; including, but not limited to customer service, credit review, account servicing, customer research, marketing, provision of IT services, and records maintenance. We give these entities access to the personal information records and files we gather to perform these functions on our behalf. These third party entities are NOT authorized to use that information for any other purpose.

Additionally, we share personal information about you when you voluntarily use certain optional services and features we offer. If you ask us to send content or a particular product to another person or entity or use a website feature that is intended to communicate with another visitor, user, customer or an affiliated business entity, we will tell that person or entity that we are sending the content, product, e-mail or other communication at your request. If you use one of our community network functions, the content of your posting will be available to all other participants to view and will be accompanied by your user name or chosen nickname.

It is possible that we or part of our business or one of our affiliates could merge with, acquire or be acquired by another business entity and your personal information could be among the assets transferred. If this occurs, you will be notified of the change by e-mail or notice on this website or one of our other services.

We reserve the right to share personal information about you with our business affiliates in the course of our business operations. We also reserve the right to share personal information about you when we believe this to be appropriate to comply with the law or in cooperation with legal authorities; to enforce the Terms and Conditions of Use governing use of this website and the terms and conditions of use governing the use of our other services; or to protect the rights, property, safety, or other interests of our visitors, users and customers. 

####### WE SOMETIMES SHARE OTHER KINDS OF INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

We may share non-personal, non-individually identifiable information about our visitors, users and customers with the group of people and entities with whom we share personal information, as well as with other third parties such as vendors, advertisers, and marketing firms. 

####### SOME INFORMATION COLLECTED CAN BE VIEWED AND CHANGED

You can review some of your personal profile at this website and correct or update it by editing your profile. You can also change personal information such as your shipping address or payment method when ordering. 

You can subscribe to or unsubscribe from e-newsletters and other promotional notices by going to the area on one of our services dealing with visitor, user or customer accounts and accessing the type of communication service you wish to change. 

You can opt out of our use of cookies to recall information about you and your computer by setting your browser not to accept cookies or to disable cookies. You cannot access or change the non-personal information that we collect. 

####### THIRD PARTY AFFINITY PROGRAMS

Occasionally, we participate in rewards programs with other business organizations where customers who are also members of these businesses will get a credit or a reward for their use or purchases from the other member organizations. We also sometimes advertise our goods, products and services on other websites or with other business entities in the form of a link so that visitors can click over to our website and purchase the services or products if they are interested. In these situations, we share information about our visitors, users and customers (including purchases) with these other member organizations and other services under the contracts these entities have with us.
